well tell me why are you staring at my
nose oh I was not staring does it
astonish you well no but no I've been
careful not to look oh and why not if
you please it disgusts you then but no I
does it color appear to you un wholesome
by no means possibly you find it just a
trifle large no small very small tiny
infinitesimal
what you accuse me of absurdity small my
nose why magnificent my nose you pug you
knob you button head know that I glory
in this nose of mine for a great nose
indicates a great man genial courteous
intellectual viril courageous whilst
that face of yours that blank Inglorious
concavity which my right hand finds on
top of you is as devoid of pride of
poetry of Soul of picturesqueness of
Contour of character of nose in short as
that which at the bottom of that limp
spine of yours my left foot oh
presently this fellow will grow
tiresome oh he blows his
horn well will no one put him in his
place if you will allow me
observe Monsieur
your nose your nose is rather
large rather oh well is that all well of
course Ah no young sir you're too simple
why you might have said a great many
things why waste your opportunity for
example thus aggressive I sir if that
nose were mine I'd have it amputate on
the spot practical how do you drink with
such a nose you must have had a cup made
especially descriptive is a rock a crag
a cape a cape say rather a
peninsula inquisitive what is that
receptacle a razor case or a
portfolio kindly ah do you love the little
birds so much that when they come and
sing to you you give them this to perch
on cautious take care a weight like that
might make you
top heavy eloquent when it blows the
typhoon howls and the clouds darken
dramatic when it
bleeds the red
sea simple eh when do they unveil the
monument military beware a secret
weapon enterprising but a sign for some
perfumer respectful sir I recognize in
you a man of Parts a man of prominence
or literary was this the nose that
launched a thousand ships these my dear
sir are things you might have said had
you some tinge of letters or a wit to
color your discourse but wit not so you
never had an atom and of letters you
need but three to write you down a s
s
ass dolt bumpkin fool how do you
do and I Cyrano
Savinien
Hercule de Bergerac