Oh have I got your attention now good
because we're adding a little something
to this month's sales contest as you all
know first prize is a Cadillac Eldorado
anybody want to see second prize second
prize a set of steak knives third prize
is you fired
they get the picture you're laughing now
you got leads Mitch & Murray paid good
money get their names to sell them you
can't close the leads you're given you
can't close [ __ ] you are [ __ ] hit the
bricks pal and beat it cuz you are going
out the leaves are weak the leaves are
weak [ __ ] leaves are weak you're weak
I've been in this business 15 years
what's your name [ __ ] you that's my name
you know why mister cuz you drove a
Hyundai to get here tonight I drove an
$80,000 BMW that's my name and your name
is your wanting and you can't play in
the man's game you can't close them and
go home and tell your wife your troubles
because only one thing counts in this
life get them to sign on the line which
is dotted you hear me you [ __ ]
[ __ ]
a.b.c they always BBC closing always be
closing always be closing
AI da attention interest decision action
attention do I have your attention
interest
are you interested I know you are cuz
it's [ __ ] or walk you close or you hit
the bricks
decision have you made your decision for
Christ an action AI da get out there you
got the prospects coming in you think
they came in to get out of the rain a
guy don't walk on the lot lest he wants
to by sitting out there waiting to give
you their money are you gonna take it
what's the problem pound Hugh Moss
you're such a hero you're so rich how
come you're coming down here waste your
time with such a bunch of bums you see
this watch you see this punch yeah that
watch costs more than your car I made
nine hundred seventy thousand dollars
last year how much you make you see pal
that's who I am and you're nothing nice
guy I don't give a [ __ ] good father [ __ ]
you go home and play with your kids you
want to work here closed you think this
is abuse you think this is abuse you
[ __ ] you can't take this how can
you take the abuse you get on a six you
don't like it leave
I can go out there tonight the materials
you got make myself $15,000 tonight in
two hours can you can you go and do
likewise AI da get mad you know what it
takes to sell real estate
it takes brass balls to sell real estate
go and do likewise gents the money's out
there you pick it up it's yours you
don't I got no