and now Mr Stark has prepared a
statement he will not be taking any
questions thank
you uh been a while since I was in front
of you I figure I'll stick to the cards
this
time there's been speculation that I was
involved in the events that occurred the
freeway and the rooftop I'm sorry Mr
shark but do you honestly expect us to
believe that that was a bodyguard and a
suit that conveniently appeared despite
the fact I know that it's confusing it
is one thing to question the official
story and another thing entirely to make
wild accusations or insinuate that I'm a
superhero I never said you a superhero
didn't well good because that would be
outlandish and uh
fantastic I I'm just not the the hero
type clearly with this uh laundry list
of Character defects all the mistakes I
made largely
public
yeah
okay truth
is I am Iron
Man