She did something that,
in our society, is unspeakable.
She kissed a black man.
Not an old uncle,
but a strong, young Negro man.
No code mattered to her
before she broke it,
but it came crashing down
on her afterwards.
The witnesses for the State,
with the exception of the
sheriff of Maycomb County.
have presented themselves
to you gentlemen, to this court...
in the cynical confidence...
that their testimony
would not be doubted.
Confident that you gentlemen
would go along with them...
on the assumption--
the evil assumption--
that all Negroes lie,
all Negroes are basically
immoral beings,
all Negro men are not
to be trusted around our women.
An assumption that one associates
with minds of their caliber,
and which is, in itself,
gentlemen, a lie,
which I do not need
to point out to you.
And so,
a quiet, humble,
respectable Negro,
who has had the unmitigated
temerity...
to feel sorry
for a white woman,
has had to put his word
against two white people's.
The defendant is not guilty,
but somebody
in this courtroom is.
Now, gentlemen,
in this country,
our courts are the great levelers.
in our courts,
all men are created equal.
i'm no idealist
to believe firmly...
in the integrity of our courts
and of our jury system.
That's no ideal to me.
That is a living, working reality !