please sit down
Ellis Boyd reading if I'll say you've
served 40 Years of a life sentence you
feel you've been
rehabilitated
rehabilitated well now let me
see you know I don't have any idea what
that
means well it means you're ready to
rejoin Society I know what you think it
means
Sunny to me it's just a madeup word
a politician's word so that young fellas
like yourself can wear a suit and a tie
and have a
job what do you really want to
know am I sorry for what I did well I
am there's not a day goes by I don't
feel
regret not because I'm in here because
you think I should
I look back on the way I was
then a
young stupid kid who committed that
terrible
crime I want to talk to
him I want to try to talk some sense to
him tell him the way things
are but I can't
that kid's long gone
and this old man is all that's
left I got to live with
that
rehabilitated it's just a
word so you go on and stamp your form
sunny and stop wasting my
time because I tell you the
truth I don't give a
for